<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Signing-ups on Material Docs</title>
    <link>http://demo.devcenter.bitrise.io.s3-website-us-east-1.amazonaws.com/signing-up/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Signing-ups on Material Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://demo.devcenter.bitrise.io.s3-website-us-east-1.amazonaws.com/signing-up/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://demo.devcenter.bitrise.io.s3-website-us-east-1.amazonaws.com/signing-up/connecting-apple-dev-account/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://demo.devcenter.bitrise.io.s3-website-us-east-1.amazonaws.com/signing-up/connecting-apple-dev-account/</guid>
      <description>Connecting Your Apple Developer Account to Bitrise You can authenticate your Apple Developer Account on Bitrise and integrate the Apple Developer Portal with your Bitrise project. This allows you to use our iOS Auto Provisioning step which makes managing Provisioning Profiles for iOS applications a lot easier!
All you need is a bitrise.io account and a valid Apple Developer Account.
Authenticating your Apple Developer Account on Bitrise  Log in to bitrise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://demo.devcenter.bitrise.io.s3-website-us-east-1.amazonaws.com/signing-up/signing-up-with-bitbucket/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://demo.devcenter.bitrise.io.s3-website-us-east-1.amazonaws.com/signing-up/signing-up-with-bitbucket/</guid>
      <description>You are able to authenticate yourself with your Bitbucket user against Bitrise. It brings some practical benefits, like logging in with one click and of course you won&amp;rsquo;t have to authorize your Bitbucket account when adding repositories hosted by these providers again.
!!! note If you&amp;rsquo;d like to sign up with your email address, please follow the instructions in signing up with email address.
Sign up Go to the Sign up page by clicking Sign up!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://demo.devcenter.bitrise.io.s3-website-us-east-1.amazonaws.com/signing-up/signing-up-with-email/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://demo.devcenter.bitrise.io.s3-website-us-east-1.amazonaws.com/signing-up/signing-up-with-email/</guid>
      <description>You can sign up to Bitrise in one step with your email address.
!!! note If you would like to use your GitHub / Bitbucket account, please check out the following devcenter articles:
* [Signing up with GitHub](/signing-up/signing-up-with-github) * [Signing up with Bitbucket](/signing-up/signing-up-with-bitbucket)  Sign up You just have to pick a username, add your email address and choose a password. Click Sign up with email.
After you provided your credentials, press Done.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://demo.devcenter.bitrise.io.s3-website-us-east-1.amazonaws.com/signing-up/signing-up-with-github/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://demo.devcenter.bitrise.io.s3-website-us-east-1.amazonaws.com/signing-up/signing-up-with-github/</guid>
      <description>You are able to authenticate yourself with your GitHub user against Bitrise. It brings some practical benefits, like logging in with one click and of course you won&amp;rsquo;t have to authorize your GitHub account when adding repositories hosted by these providers again.
!!! note If you&amp;rsquo;d like to sign up with your email address, please follow the instructions in signing up with email address.
Sign up Go to the Sign up page by clicking Sign up!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://demo.devcenter.bitrise.io.s3-website-us-east-1.amazonaws.com/signing-up/trial-after-signing-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://demo.devcenter.bitrise.io.s3-website-us-east-1.amazonaws.com/signing-up/trial-after-signing-up/</guid>
      <description>After you have created your account on Bitrise it will start with a 14-day trial of the Team plan. This means that you can setup your application and start building it with all the benefits of the paying plan.
You can see the remaining time of your trial in the header.
!!! note &amp;ldquo;Tip&amp;rdquo; Read more about optimizing your build times to help you fit into the 10 minute limit for free accounts.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>